all righty today city challenge withdraw
L mandatory head shots reinforce dos and
explosive Revenge so it's time for
withdraw again where we're going to talk
about random stuff for 4 minutes because
Sparrow takes way too long to show up so
we're just going to start off by uh
giving cyber tree Med kits and then yeah
then we're going to blow up a hole
through the wall and we are going to
cyber cyber I don't think that's how you
do the mission you know just saying you
might want to like yeah
perfect all right
hi there guys I'm not actually a fan of
being blown
up there we go oh why are you here
huh I for I actually have to shoot these
SCS now because
uh I don't have enough Thumper shots to
shoot them for fun and just to kind of
save my time a bit then again it doesn't
really save my time because I I I don't
have Mastery pugs because I am not
respecing for this so yeah let's get out
of there and we're going to have two sh
pump in there all right one and two now
we can drop that and we are about to
find out if I have somehow really really
really bad aim and I somehow messed it
up the answer is probably oh never mind
no yep sure okay so cyber's going to go
work on a cage right now and we're just
going to hope it works out I guess and
yeah all right getting the
bags and uh cyber this is not promising
yet
know I I don't I'm not sure I like this
feeling oh okay s got a cage get in
here this is not great honestly it's not
great for cyber right
now oh there oh no cyber's alive oh wow
okay we'll see where this
goes still fighting why are you still
fighting units down here
I'm just going to go get a last cash
back honestly that's basically it and we
get the floating cash bag again this
always happens at some
point there we go cyber don't get shot
now that will not be
ideal I'm going to back away from that
um essentially a grenade yeah all right
move
up this is
fine why are there explosives for both
of them like okay no you don't you're
not included in that don't join them I
do not appreciate that and I will not
like you because of
that all right here we go uh now cyber's
just going to bring up all the bags and
that one that got flung down all the way
by an explosive so uh
yeah you if y'all could show up that
would actually be fantastic you
know hi
there
there is one bit of s97 ammo and I am
taking it thank you very much I should
also take a cash back too that would
actually help and uh yeah cyber when you
show up we can probably move you
know hi
there hi
there
oh there were explosives involved it's
fine I got free ammo and um cyber you
ready move all right let's go then
hopefully there are more units which
there are because none of us bother to
count
because we're very very smart of our
decisions there we go all
right why are you here
hello I'm going to move thank you very
much and I'm going to heal up a bit just
so I don't uh you know
die cuz it tends to work out better when
that doesn't
happen I'm going to dip actually yeah
cyber if you want to like
okay why do you have to get me with the
flashbang of all
things
PE I feel like I know where the units
are okay there they are never mind they
walk into me that's what
happens hi cyber I got this check this
out why am I going this
way why am I going that way no no I'm
going to go get my yeah I'm going to go
get my Med kit back thank you very much
that would actually be helpful for all
of us all right okay
so uh cyber definitely needs a med kit
oh
wow cyber there you
go cyber Med
kit cyber you're doing it again take
your med kit all right now we just wait
it's going to be wave right now for real
isn't
it I'm going to make I'm going to make
the very very City choice and move right
now
yep there it
is cyber get
moving literally get moving it's
literally a new wave show up cyber get
it come on I don't want to watch this
side I have to watch that side okay y
get down here all right that was um
interesting uh I'm going to let cyber
take it from here and they are going to
take they're going to talk about the
most boring stuff ever get in here yeah
all
right cyber you know you know the thing
yeah
yeah so it's basically going to be about
2023 and um 2024 starting and it's going
to be some really really bad
opinions I mean yeah it has
okay I apologize to the people looking
at this on phone and not reading any of
this but sucks to be you I might read
them out
all right so yeah 2024 really has no not
2024 what am I thinking 2023 has gone by
really quickly 2024 hasn't even started
yet I mean when you watch it probably
will just think it's an Eastern
Standard what you expect was going to
happen Americans are like what 12 hours
behind the
world okay look we're just going to make
a really really really bad insult at
them the script ends
here you didn't get a script that's the
exact point oh hi hi there
mate
cyber
uh
improv I don't know don't ask me I have
no confidence in what I am saying right
now all right uh so basically 2023 G by
really really fast
and
anym hi there guys nice to meet you
absolutely oh never mind you come sber
just talk about random stuff it's not
that
difficult all right talk about hitting
two hitting
one0 oh hi guys y'all aren't supposed to
do that that's not
allowed I am not happy about
that there we go if you
what do you mean it'll be
okay unless you go to
Alaska or Alaska you know I don't even
know how to pronounce that word I Alaska
yeah probably just that you know what uh
unless
it's this video is probably just going
to be up at midnight that time so uh if
you live in
AKA Anchorage daylight time yes or anry
Standard time I have no idea what is
daylight savings right now and I do not
care uh the last one was about daylight
savings actually so
yeah it would be
funny it
would I'm talking okay I I I need to get
an ammo thank you very much I I realized
this a wave break cyber where have
you cyber you suck wow jump scaring me
unintentionally so I try not to get
sniped at the end this
time okay and uh yeah I don't know what
do you think of 2023 it's just like
another year again it wasn't that bad I
mean AI started becoming a really really
accessible
thing a funny rich person decides to buy
a social media company and rebrands it
horribly but someone had to ruin
it I'm sorry I didn't ruin anything oh
hi there
buddy absolutely not s could I get one
actually thank you very
much s can I get one like can I get one
Med
kit you know just to make my life easier
I would appreciate a med
kit oh hi there Sparrow all right
Sparrow's here
and I honestly have absolutely no idea
what we're going to do all right
uh want to just rush
it rush it cyber all right we're rushing
it thank you very very
much I am not makeing good choice assor
result there we
go all right cyber now show up and don't
get shot all right d no cyber died again
cyber died again no I'm pretty sure I
saw cyber die again again but sber
didn't B get sniped and that's the daily
challenge done in under 9 minutes and 45
seconds this is incredible we're going
to replay this and have a Happy New Year
cheers everyone have a great
[Music]
time